tweetbinder.com 2018-06-22

# Tweet Binder - Privacy

At Tweet Category S.L. (from now on, Tweet Binder) we take very serious your data protection and we are committed with their privacy. This update explains how Tweet Binder manages and storages the data it has from its users and clients. In this document you will also find how you can exercise your privacy rights. Notice that you can reach out to us directly by emailing [legal@tweetbinder.com](mailto:legal@tweetbinder.com) with any issues or questions regarding your data and how we use them.

### What data does Tweet Binder storages and why

Tweet Binder storages the minimum data necessary in order for its users and clients to use the platform and analyze terms on Twitter or Instagram.

We gather the following data of the free users that login Tweet Binder:

  * User’s Twitter Name
  * Name that user has given to Twitter
  * Number of followers of the user in the moment he does login
  * Location the user has given in Twitter
  * First login date
  * User’s Twitter token
  * Date of his last report
  * Reports generated in the platform
  * Profile picture of the user
  * Cookie of the browser

All these data are gathered through Twitter’s API. The login in Twee Binder with Twitter’s API is mandatory to be able to create reports. This is because Twitter Inc. obliges to access to public data (tweets tt go inside the report) through a Twitter account. At Tweet Binder we use the user’s account for that purpose. If the user wants to, he can as well provide us the following data:

  * Email
  * Company’s name
  * VAT number
  * Address
  * City
  * ZIP code
  * Country

This second round of data is not mandatory to create reports in the platform. Tweet Binder gives users the chance of providing these data so that if they want to purchase something in the future they don’t have to give them again.

From the clients (those who have at least purchased once a Tweet Binder product) Tweet Binder gathers the following data:

  * User’s Twitter Name
  * Name that user has given to Twitter
  * Number of followers of the user in the moment he does login
  * Location the user has given in Twitter
  * First login date
  * User’s Twitter token
  * Date of his last report
  * Reports generated in the platform
  * Profile picture of the user
  * Email
  * Company
  * VAT number
  * Address
  * City
  * ZIP code
  * Country
  * Cookie of the browser

These data are necessary to generate the reports and the invoices of the purchases.

About the payment methods, Tweet Binder does not storage any data at the moment (credit cards, PayPal accounts, etc.). This function is delegated in the payment platform BrainTree, property of PayPal. This platform keeps those data secure.

Tweet Binder access through Twitter’s API to public data (those data visible to any kind of user) of each tweet and user who has tweeted with the term analyzed in the report. The data gathered and analyzed by Tweet Binder are the ones obtained through the API and that can be found here: <https://developer.twitter.com/en/docs/tweets/data-dictionary/overview/tweet-objectTweet> Binder deletes the information of the reports after 7 days.

All the information gathered about a tweet is necessary to create the well-known Tweet Binder reports. These reports analyze the impact and reach of a hashtag, account or keyword on Twitter.

At any time the user can contact Tweet Binder to erase all his user data.

Tweet Binder obtains Twitter’s public data trough two different APis:

  * Public API: for free users
  * PowerTrack API: for pay users

The professional API, PowerTrack, analyzes information with a greater date range.

### Web browser cookies

Tweet Binder may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the site may not function properly.

### Security

For Tweet Binder, keeping its users’ and clients’ data safe is vital and the company makes an effort in order for them to be protected. That is why we have implemented technical and organizational measures to keep them safe.

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices an security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.

### How we use collected information

Tweet Binder may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * To improve customer service Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
  * To personalize user experience We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
  * To improve our Site We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
  * To process payments We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
  * To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
  * To send periodic emails We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.

Tweet Binder won’t contact its users or clients for any more than necessary for the correct functioning of the site and to give them the best service.

Tweet Binder, in some cases, could use the user’s Twitter token to complete some info of a report such us number of Retweets, profile picture, etc. Any person or any client can write to Tweet Binder asking to not receive any email about the company. Users receive an email whenever their plan is automatically renewed same as when someone purchases a product from the website. This email has only informative value.

Tweet Binder will never ask you to give any sensible information such us family related, racial or any other personal data. The company will never do so. Tweet Binder only wants for its users to have a great experience.

Through the browser’s cookie and the platform Google Analytics we measure the visits and users behavior. This info is anonymous. This cookies policy is accepted in the platform.

### Data protection rights

At any moment, users and clients can ask Tweet Binder to:

  * Edit his data
  * Totally or partially erase his data
  * Say which data the company has about the user

### Who does Tweet Binder share its users’ and clients’ data with

With no one. Tweet Binder does not share with any institution, company, organization or particular its users’ data.

### Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

### Changes to this privacy policy

Tweet Binder has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

### Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

### Tweet Binder contact

You have several ways of contacting with Tweet Binder:

  * Phone: +34 610528073
  * Address: Travesía M. de Zilbeti 1 – 8A Pamplona – Spain
  * Email: [legal@tweetbinder.com](mailto:legal@tweetbinder.com)

This document was last updated on May 24, 2018

* * *

We do not issue refunds for digital products once the order is confirmed and the plan or report is purchased. We recommend contacting us for assistance if you experience any issues receiving or downloading our products. We will help you along the process.

If you have any questions about our Returns and Refunds Policy, please contact us: [legal@tweetbinder.com](mailto:legal@tweetbinder.com)

Thanks for your time.
